[
    {
        "question": "WhatCAPRICIOUS-colorCANTALOUPE-isNONCHALANT-theINFINITY-sky?",
        "answer": " Blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatDIAPHANOUS-doIRIDESCENT-youTENACIOUS-useMAGNANIMOUS-toSOLITUDE-writeWISTFUL-with?",
        "answer": " Pen"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatQUELL-doVIBRANCY-youCRYPTIC-useDILEMMA-toPALETTE-cutEBULLIENT-paper?",
        "answer": " Scissors"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCOMPASSION-doMACAROON-youENIGMA-wearMARMALADE-onLANGUID-yourJOCUND-feet?",
        "answer": " Shoes"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatLISSOME-doSCRABBLE-youCOCKTAIL-useXENIAL-toLISSOME-measureLOZENGE-time?",
        "answer": " Clock"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatNONPLUSSED-doRAVENOUS-youDILEMMA-useRESOLUTE-toIDIOSYNCRASY-communicateTRANSLUCENT-withRHAPSODY-othersINQUISITIVE-overDILIGENT-distance?",
        "answer": " Phone"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatHUMMINGBIRD-isLUMINESCENT-theAQUAMARINE-oppositeSCRABBLE-ofRANCOROUS-hot?",
        "answer": " Cold"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatWHIRLWIND-isTICKLE-theSURREAL-oppositeRESILIENCE-ofGEYSER-up?",
        "answer": " Down"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatTENACIOUS-doSTETHOSCOPE-youIRREVERENT-useINSATIABLE-toJUXTAPOSITION-cleanLUMINOUS-yourREVERIE-teeth?",
        "answer": " Toothbrush"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatTIRAMISU-doCURIOSITY-youEUPHORIA-useBELIEF-toSAGACITY-washVERDANT-yourRAVIOLI-hands?",
        "answer": " Soap"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatFRIVOLOUS-doRAVENOUS-youSAGACIOUS-useXENOPHOBIC-toMELANCHOLIC-seeCIRCUITOUS-thingsPERCEPTION-farARDENT-away?",
        "answer": " Binoculars"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatETHEREAL-doTANTAMOUNT-youRESILIENCE-useSURREPTITIOUS-toSERENADE-seeCONUNDRUM-thingsGROTTO-upTRANQUILITY-close?",
        "answer": " Magnifying glass"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatMYRIAD-doETHEREAL-youGRANDIOSE-useBACKPACK-toOMINOUS-protectSERENADE-yourDIAPHANOUS-eyesEMPATHY-fromINSCRUTABLE-theDELIRIOUS-sun?",
        "answer": " Sunglasses"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCHANDELIER-doINQUISITIVE-youEXACERBATE-useMANTLE-toEQUANIMITY-makeINSUPERABLE-aHARMONIOUS-phoneINEFFABLE-call?",
        "answer": " Smartphone"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatEXHILARATING-doCURIOSITY-youEGALITARIAN-useRESOLUTE-toRHAPSODY-writeDIAPHANOUS-onTENACITY-aRESILIENCE-whiteboard?",
        "answer": " Marker"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatEGALITARIAN-doCURIOSITY-youARCANE-useCIRCUITOUS-toTURBULENT-eraseLUMINOUS-somethingILLUSION-youSAUNA-wroteCHAOS-onTICKLE-aCROISSANT-whiteboard?",
        "answer": " Eraser"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatEXQUISITE-doZEALOUS-youCHAOS-useSEISMIC-toABHORRENT-keepHACKNEYED-foodDEVOTION-fresh?",
        "answer": " Refrigerator"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatEUPHORIA-doEPHEMERAL-youOMELET-useORNATE-toXENOPHOBIC-cookBONNET-foodPENSIVE-with?",
        "answer": " Stove"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCOLANDER-doLANGUID-youWHISKER-useCACOPHONY-toGRANDIOSE-cleanESCAPADE-theMARMALADE-floor?",
        "answer": " Mop"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatSERENDIPITY-doUNPREDICTABLE-youFLAMINGO-useECLIPSE-toDISILLUSIONMENT-dryECLECTIC-yourDAPPER-hands?",
        "answer": " Towel"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatINSUPERABLE-doAPRON-youPICKLE-useLACKADAISICAL-toINTRIGUE-cutDAUNTING-vegetables?",
        "answer": " Knife"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCONUNDRUM-doSANCTIMONIOUS-youOBDURATE-useMALEVOLENT-toJUXTAPOSE-makeRANCOROUS-coffee?",
        "answer": " Coffeemaker"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatICICLE-doFANCIFUL-youLUGGAGE-useLACKADAISICAL-toSERENDIPITY-heatGLITTERING-foodRESOLUTE-quickly?",
        "answer": " Microwave"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatLUGGAGE-doSCRUMPTIOUS-youINFINITY-useEARMUFF-toBLIMP-browseLUGGAGE-theLANGUID-internet?",
        "answer": " Browser"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatORNATE-doSCOOP-youGEYSER-useSAUNA-toENTICING-sendGLITTERING-andAMUSEMENT-receiveVIBRANT-emails?",
        "answer": " Email"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatSCRUMPTIOUS-doFENDER-youWHIRLWIND-useINSIDIOUS-toNEBULOUS-chargeDILIGENT-yourSAXOPHONE-phone?",
        "answer": " Charger"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatPERCEPTION-doCONUNDRUM-youTUXEDO-usePIQUANT-toPALETTE-storeWREATH-picturesSCRABBLE-andDILIGENT-documents?",
        "answer": " Computer"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatTHISTLE-doEXHILARATING-youTANTAMOUNT-useDAUNTING-toPARADOX-listenVIBRANCY-toSURREPTITIOUS-music?",
        "answer": " Headphones"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatVEXATIOUS-doMELANCHOLY-youZANY-useANTICIPATION-toRHAPSODY-measureENRICHING-temperature?",
        "answer": " Thermometer"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatNEBULOUS-doVERBOSE-youINTRIGUE-useIDYLLIC-toCONJURE-checkECLIPSED-yourJUBILANT-weight?",
        "answer": " Scale"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatDISCOMBOBULATED-doCAPRICIOUS-youEXACERBATE-useTENACIOUS-toINSIDIOUS-openZEPHYR-aIMPRESSIONABLE-door?",
        "answer": " Handle"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatRADIANCE-doINFINITY-youJUBILANT-useCOCKTAIL-toAMUSEMENT-turnRAMBUNCTIOUS-aSUPERFLUOUS-lightAARDVARK-on/off?",
        "answer": " Switch"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCHIRP-doWINSOME-youCARAMEL-usePENSIVE-toBELLIGERENT-fastenDAUNTING-yourTANTAMOUNT-pants?",
        "answer": " Button"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatREVELATION-doINFINITY-youMELANCHOLY-useCUCUMBER-toEARMUFF-tieGOSSAMER-yourWHISKER-shoes?",
        "answer": " Lace"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatWRY-doDAUNTING-youINTRIGUE-useFJORD-toQUELL-holdSAXOPHONE-papersDRIZZLE-together?",
        "answer": " Clip"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatMINGLE-doTICKLE-youQUIXOTIC-useQUIXOTIC-toMANTLE-writeMAGNANIMOUS-onANCHOVY-paper?",
        "answer": " Pen"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatDIAPHANOUS-doCAPRICIOUS-youBISCUIT-useTUXEDO-toCHUTNEY-carryIMPRESSIONABLE-groceries?",
        "answer": " Bag"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCHANDELIER-doPERCEPTION-youQUIXOTIC-useINEPTITUDE-toVERBOSE-keepXENIAL-yourCONJURE-foodBANGLE-hot?",
        "answer": " Oven"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatOMINOUS-doYEARNING-youTRANQUILITY-useWISTFUL-toDILIGENT-keepIRIDESCENT-yourSERENDIPITY-foodEXTRANEOUS-cold?",
        "answer": " Fridge"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatFJORD-doRETICENT-youWREATH-useMYSTICAL-toHAUNTING-watchFLAMINGO-aGROTTO-movie?",
        "answer": " Television"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatTURBULENT-doXENIAL-youAQUAMARINE-useMAGNANIMOUS-toBELLIGERENT-washDEVOTION-yourMINGLE-clothes?",
        "answer": " Washer"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCOMPOSURE-doMELANCHOLY-youOBDURATE-useTRUFFLE-toAQUAMARINE-dryBELLIGERENT-yourSERENADE-clothes?",
        "answer": " Dryer"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatWISTFUL-doQUIVER-youVELOCITY-useINSCRUTABLE-toVIBRANT-unlockUNPREDICTABLE-yourDAFFODIL-car?",
        "answer": " Key"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCONVOLUTED-doCONUNDRUM-youCIRCUITOUS-useVENTURE-toMELLIFLUOUS-stopREVERENT-yourBENIGN-car?",
        "answer": " Brake"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatINSCRUTABLE-doASPARAGUS-youRAMBUNCTIOUS-useTANGERINE-toAESTHETIC-movePARASOL-yourPIQUANT-car?",
        "answer": " Steering"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatVIVACIOUS-doGEYSER-youEUPHORIC-useSCRUMPTIOUS-toSQUIGGLE-findANTICIPATION-directions?",
        "answer": " Map"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatVIVACIOUS-doBANGLE-youRESOLUTE-useENIGMA-toSYMPHONY-bookZEALOUS-aBITTERSWEET-flight?",
        "answer": " Ticket"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatSERENDIPITY-doINEPTITUDE-youENTHRALLING-useDOLPHIN-toMELLIFLUOUS-payAUDACIOUS-forRECKLESS-things?",
        "answer": " Money"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatFUCHSIA-doVIBRANT-youSURREPTITIOUS-useCURSORY-toBUMBLEBEE-exerciseCACOPHONY-atSKYSCRAPER-home?",
        "answer": " Mat"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatBELIEF-doVERBOSE-youWHIMSICAL-useRACONTEUR-toBUCOLIC-openVEXATIOUS-aEGALITARIAN-can?",
        "answer": " Can opener"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatSURREPTITIOUS-doFURTIVE-youDAFFODIL-usePERSPICACIOUS-toINEPTITUDE-drinkENIGMA-water?",
        "answer": " Cup"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatDILEMMA-doMAJESTIC-youINEPTITUDE-useMALEVOLENT-toCACOPHONY-eatXENIAL-soup?",
        "answer": " Spoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatECCENTRIC-doDISPARATE-youLUMINESCENT-useENIGMATIC-toBLIMP-cutANTITHESIS-aRETICENT-steak?",
        "answer": " Knife"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatZANY-doCONUNDRUM-youACERBIC-usePENSIVE-toREDEMPTION-eatSERENITY-sushi?",
        "answer": " Chopsticks"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatJUXTAPOSITION-doYEARNING-youQUIRKY-useQUIZZICAL-toZEST-eatSUPERFLUOUS-salad?",
        "answer": " Fork"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatGROTTO-doTURBULENT-youMEZZANINE-useENTHRALLING-toSQUIGGLE-holdVEXATIOUS-aJOCUND-sandwichSCINTILLATING-together?",
        "answer": " Toothpick"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatGRANDIOSE-doSADDLE-youGROTTO-useARCANE-toQUIRKY-drinkTACTILE-coffee?",
        "answer": " Mug"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatIMAGINATION-doDAPPER-youYEARNING-useCONJURE-toRAMBUNCTIOUS-drinkHELICOPTER-soda?",
        "answer": " Straw"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCURIOSITY-doPARADOX-youNOSTALGIA-useGRUMBLE-toINFINITY-eatMELLOWNESS-iceINSUPERABLE-cream?",
        "answer": " Spoon"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatNOSTALGIA-doANTICIPATION-youINSIDIOUS-useREVERIE-toAMBIVALENCE-eatLUGGAGE-pizza?",
        "answer": " Slice"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatMELLOWNESS-doWHISKER-youRAVIOLI-usePICKLE-toDANDELION-startEPHEMERAL-aVENTURE-fire?",
        "answer": " Match"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatVIBRANCY-doALCHEMY-youEMPATHY-useEPHEMERAL-toINSIDIOUS-putPEPPERMINT-outTURTLENECK-aSURREPTITIOUS-fire?",
        "answer": " Water"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatLANGUID-doFLAMINGO-youQUOTIDIAN-useAMUSEMENT-toASPARAGUS-openREDEMPTION-aMELANCHOLIC-bottle?",
        "answer": " Bottle opener"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatIMAGINATION-doELUSIVE-youBACKPACK-useTEMPESTUOUS-toYEARNING-writeRESOLUTE-onCLANDESTINE-aPALETTE-chalkboard?",
        "answer": " Chalk"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatRETICENT-doZEALOUS-youCHAMELEON-useTANGERINE-toCIRCUITOUS-cleanCONVOLUTED-theCHUTNEY-dishes?",
        "answer": " Sponge"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatOMINOUS-doTRAMPOLINE-youINEPTITUDE-useTEMPESTUOUS-toMELLIFLUOUS-wipeQUINTESSENTIAL-aVENTURE-surface?",
        "answer": " Rag"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatPIQUANT-doSERENDIPITY-youEPHEMERAL-usePEPPERMINT-toQUIXOTIC-sweepTRANSLUCENT-theWRY-floor?",
        "answer": " Broom"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatTANGERINE-doYEARNING-youGLITTERING-useCOCKTAIL-toREVERENT-mopCHAMELEON-theEGALITARIAN-floor?",
        "answer": " Bucket"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatCOMPASSION-doLACKADAISICAL-youCAPITULATE-useILLUSION-toBANGLE-removeMELLIFLUOUS-dust?",
        "answer": " Dustpan"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatEGALITARIAN-doNONPLUSSED-youGEYSER-useTACTILE-toICICLE-lightMAGNANIMOUS-upMALEVOLENT-aMAGNANIMOUS-room?",
        "answer": " Lamp"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatPERCEPTION-doCHAMELEON-youZANY-usePICKLE-toINCORRIGIBLE-unlockECLIPSED-yourHACKNEYED-phone?",
        "answer": " Password"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatREVERIE-doTIRAMISU-youAMUSEMENT-useXENOPHOBIC-toFJORD-takeSTETHOSCOPE-aENRICHING-picture?",
        "answer": " Camera"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatBONNET-doRECKLESS-youPICKLE-useQUIVER-toANTICIPATION-playPAJAMAS-musicTERRARIUM-inCOMPOSURE-yourCURSORY-car?",
        "answer": " Radio"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatENRICHING-doTENACIOUS-youSURREAL-useINFINITY-toDELIRIOUS-checkLUDICROUS-theMOSAIC-time?",
        "answer": " Watch"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatSERENITY-doCHAOS-youSARDONIC-useALPACA-toIRREVOCABLE-sendLUGGAGE-aSKYSCRAPER-textZENITH-message?",
        "answer": " Messenger"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatVULTURE-doLUMINOUS-youVENTURE-useOBDURATE-toEPHEMERAL-payOSTENTATIOUS-forTERRARIUM-thingsGOSSAMER-online?",
        "answer": " PayPal"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatFANCIFUL-doJUBILATION-youVERBOSE-useRECKLESS-toSURREAL-findXENIAL-aVIBRANT-location?",
        "answer": " GPS"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatFUCHSIA-doCAPRICIOUS-youINEPTITUDE-useWRY-toSUPERCILIOUS-searchJUBILANT-theFJORD-internet?",
        "answer": " Google"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatEFFERVESCENT-doNARWHAL-youFERVENT-useGEYSER-toHARMONIOUS-editENRICHING-aRADIANT-photo?",
        "answer": " Photoshop"
    },
    {
        "question": "WhatGARGOYLE-doHARBINGER-youMIRAGE-useQUIRKY-toMIRAGE-createWHISKER-aVIVACIOUS-document?",
        "answer": " Word"
    }
]